<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Art for Charity on Seraphine Arts</title><link>https://seraphine-arts.com/en/charity/</link><description>Recent content in Art for Charity on Seraphine Arts</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:34:59 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seraphine-arts.com/en/charity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sky Dragon - 2024</title><link>https://seraphine-arts.com/en/charity/2024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:34:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://seraphine-arts.com/en/charity/2024/</guid><description>With the new design for the &amp;ldquo;Year of the Dragon&amp;rdquo; according to the Asian lunar calendar, the collaboration with the LOAN Foundation (LOAN Stiftung) and the joint aid project for 2024 enters its third round.
As before, the entire profit from this collection will go towards supporting the poorest children in Vietnam and will be donated quarterly.</description></item><item><title>Reflection - 2023</title><link>https://seraphine-arts.com/en/charity/2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 19:34:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://seraphine-arts.com/en/charity/2023/</guid><description>Just as the light of the sun lets the moon shine, our world reflects the good we do. Inspired by the Vietnamese Lunar Year of the Cat, the two-part set &amp;ldquo;Reflection&amp;rdquo; continues the &amp;ldquo;art for charity&amp;rdquo; project and cooperation with the LOAN Foundation (LOAN Stiftung) in 2023.
Like before, all profits from this collection will be donated quarterly to the LOAN Stiftung to support children in need.
Update July 2023: Thank you for an amazing first six months!</description></item><item><title>Dawn - 2022</title><link>https://seraphine-arts.com/en/charity/2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 19:34:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://seraphine-arts.com/en/charity/2022/</guid><description>Inspired by the Lunar New Year of the Tiger 2022, I created the illustration &amp;ldquo;DAWN&amp;rdquo; as the first motif of the art for charity cooperation with the LOAN Foundation (LOAN Stiftung). &amp;ldquo;DAWN&amp;rdquo; will be exclusively available throughout the Lunar Year of the Tiger, with all funds being transferred to the LOAN Foundation every quarter.
Update February 2022: Thanks to your amazing support we were able to raise 340€ and make our first donation.</description></item></channel></rss>